D:\boot  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\efi  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\support  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\boot\en-us  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\boot\fonts  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\boot\resources  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\efi\boot  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\efi\microsoft  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\efi\microsoft\boot  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\efi\microsoft\boot\fonts  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\efi\microsoft\boot\resources  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\dlmanifests  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\en-us  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\etwproviders  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\inf  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\migration  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\replacementmanifests  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\sxs  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\vista  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\xp  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\dlmanifests\microsoft-activedirectory-webservices-dl  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\dlmanifests\microsoft-windows-bluetooth-config  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\dlmanifests\microsoft-windows-com-complus-setup-dl  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\dlmanifests\microsoft-windows-com-dtc-setup-dl  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\dlmanifests\microsoft-windows-dhcpservermigplugin-dl  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\dlmanifests\microsoft-windows-directoryservices-adam-dl  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\dlmanifests\microsoft-windows-iasserver-migplugin  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\dlmanifests\microsoft-windows-ie-clientnetworkprotocolimplementation-migration  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\dlmanifests\microsoft-windows-iis-dl  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\dlmanifests\microsoft-windows-internet-naming-service-runtime  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\dlmanifests\microsoft-windows-msmq-messagingcoreservice  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\dlmanifests\microsoft-windows-networkbridge  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\dlmanifests\microsoft-windows-networkloadbalancing-core  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\dlmanifests\microsoft-windows-rasconnectionmanager  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\dlmanifests\microsoft-windows-rasserver-migplugin  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\dlmanifests\microsoft-windows-tapisetup  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\dlmanifests\microsoft-windows-terminalservices-licenseserver  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\dlmanifests\microsoft-windows-textservicesframework-migration-dl  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\dlmanifests\microsoft-windows-unimodem-config  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\dlmanifests\microsoft-windows-winsock-core-infrastructure-upgrade  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\dlmanifests\microsoft-windows-wmi-core  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\dlmanifests\networking-mpssvc-svc  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\etwproviders\en-us  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\migration\wtr  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\replacementmanifests\hwvid-migration-2  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-activedirectory-webservices  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-client-license-platform-service-migration  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-onecore-tiledatarepository  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-windows-appmanagement-migration  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-windows-appx-deployment-server  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-windows-audio-mmecore-other  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-windows-bth-user  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-windows-com-complus-setup  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-windows-deviceassociationframeworkmigration  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-windows-directoryservices-adam-client  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-windows-iis-rm  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-windows-mapscontrol-migration  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-windows-mup  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-windows-network-setup  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-windows-offlinefiles-core  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-windows-pnpmigration  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-windows-rasapi-mig  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-windows-rasserver-migplugin  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-windows-security-ngc-localaccountmigplugin  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-windows-shmig  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-windows-sxs  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-windows-tcpip  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-windows-terminalservices-appserver-licensing  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-windows-terminalservices-licenseserver  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-windows-textservicesframework-migration  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-windows-virtualization-vmswitch  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\replacementmanifests\networkbridge  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\replacementmanifests\networking-mpssvc-svc  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\replacementmanifests\printing-localprinting-replacement  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\replacementmanifests\sppmig  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\replacementmanifests\windowssearchengine  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\replacementmanifests\wpc  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-windows-offlinefiles-core\en-us  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-windows-shmig\en-us  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-windows-sxs\en-us  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\support\adfs  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\support\adprep  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\support\logging  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\support\samples  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\support\adfs\en-us  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\support\adprep\en-us  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\support\logging\en-us  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
DC1.Kredit.Dylan.local
DC2.Kredit.Dylan.local
C:\
D:\
D:\boot  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\boot\en-us  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\boot\fonts  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\boot\resources  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\efi  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\efi\boot  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\efi\microsoft  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\efi\microsoft\boot  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\efi\microsoft\boot\fonts  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\efi\microsoft\boot\resources  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\dlmanifests  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\en-us  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\etwproviders  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\inf  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\migration  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\replacementmanifests  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\sxs  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\vista  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\xp  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\dlmanifests\microsoft-activedirectory-webservices-dl  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\dlmanifests\microsoft-windows-bluetooth-config  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\dlmanifests\microsoft-windows-com-complus-setup-dl  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\dlmanifests\microsoft-windows-com-dtc-setup-dl  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\dlmanifests\microsoft-windows-dhcpservermigplugin-dl  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\dlmanifests\microsoft-windows-directoryservices-adam-dl  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\dlmanifests\microsoft-windows-iasserver-migplugin  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\dlmanifests\microsoft-windows-ie-clientnetworkprotocolimplementation-migration  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\dlmanifests\microsoft-windows-iis-dl  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\dlmanifests\microsoft-windows-internet-naming-service-runtime  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\dlmanifests\microsoft-windows-msmq-messagingcoreservice  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\dlmanifests\microsoft-windows-networkbridge  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\dlmanifests\microsoft-windows-networkloadbalancing-core  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\dlmanifests\microsoft-windows-rasconnectionmanager  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\dlmanifests\microsoft-windows-rasserver-migplugin  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\dlmanifests\microsoft-windows-tapisetup  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\dlmanifests\microsoft-windows-terminalservices-licenseserver  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\dlmanifests\microsoft-windows-textservicesframework-migration-dl  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\dlmanifests\microsoft-windows-unimodem-config  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\dlmanifests\microsoft-windows-winsock-core-infrastructure-upgrade  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\dlmanifests\microsoft-windows-wmi-core  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\dlmanifests\networking-mpssvc-svc  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\etwproviders\en-us  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\migration\wtr  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\replacementmanifests\hwvid-migration-2  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-activedirectory-webservices  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-client-license-platform-service-migration  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-onecore-tiledatarepository  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-windows-appmanagement-migration  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-windows-appx-deployment-server  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-windows-audio-mmecore-other  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-windows-bth-user  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-windows-com-complus-setup  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-windows-deviceassociationframeworkmigration  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-windows-directoryservices-adam-client  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-windows-iis-rm  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-windows-mapscontrol-migration  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-windows-mup  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-windows-network-setup  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-windows-offlinefiles-core  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-windows-pnpmigration  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-windows-rasapi-mig  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-windows-rasserver-migplugin  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-windows-security-ngc-localaccountmigplugin  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-windows-shmig  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-windows-sxs  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-windows-tcpip  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-windows-terminalservices-appserver-licensing  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-windows-terminalservices-licenseserver  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-windows-textservicesframework-migration  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-windows-virtualization-vmswitch  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\replacementmanifests\networkbridge  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\replacementmanifests\networking-mpssvc-svc  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\replacementmanifests\printing-localprinting-replacement  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\replacementmanifests\sppmig  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\replacementmanifests\windowssearchengine  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\replacementmanifests\wpc  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-windows-offlinefiles-core\en-us  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-windows-shmig\en-us  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-windows-sxs\en-us  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\support  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\support\adfs  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\support\adprep  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\support\logging  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\support\samples  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\support\adfs\en-us  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\support\adprep\en-us  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
D:\support\logging\en-us  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
FS.Kredit.Dylan.local
B:\
B:\boot  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\boot\en-us  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\boot\fonts  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\boot\resources  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\efi  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\efi\boot  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\efi\microsoft  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\efi\microsoft\boot  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\efi\microsoft\boot\fonts  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\efi\microsoft\boot\resources  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\sources  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\sources\dlmanifests  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\sources\en-us  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\sources\etwproviders  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\sources\inf  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\sources\migration  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\sources\replacementmanifests  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\sources\sxs  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\sources\vista  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\sources\xp  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\sources\dlmanifests\microsoft-activedirectory-webservices-dl  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\sources\dlmanifests\microsoft-windows-bluetooth-config  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\sources\dlmanifests\microsoft-windows-com-complus-setup-dl  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\sources\dlmanifests\microsoft-windows-com-dtc-setup-dl  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\sources\dlmanifests\microsoft-windows-dhcpservermigplugin-dl  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\sources\dlmanifests\microsoft-windows-directoryservices-adam-dl  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\sources\dlmanifests\microsoft-windows-iasserver-migplugin  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\sources\dlmanifests\microsoft-windows-ie-clientnetworkprotocolimplementation-migration  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\sources\dlmanifests\microsoft-windows-iis-dl  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\sources\dlmanifests\microsoft-windows-internet-naming-service-runtime  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\sources\dlmanifests\microsoft-windows-msmq-messagingcoreservice  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\sources\dlmanifests\microsoft-windows-networkbridge  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\sources\dlmanifests\microsoft-windows-networkloadbalancing-core  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\sources\dlmanifests\microsoft-windows-rasconnectionmanager  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\sources\dlmanifests\microsoft-windows-rasserver-migplugin  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\sources\dlmanifests\microsoft-windows-tapisetup  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\sources\dlmanifests\microsoft-windows-terminalservices-licenseserver  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\sources\dlmanifests\microsoft-windows-textservicesframework-migration-dl  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\sources\dlmanifests\microsoft-windows-unimodem-config  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\sources\dlmanifests\microsoft-windows-winsock-core-infrastructure-upgrade  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\sources\dlmanifests\microsoft-windows-wmi-core  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\sources\dlmanifests\networking-mpssvc-svc  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\sources\etwproviders\en-us  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\sources\migration\wtr  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\sources\replacementmanifests\hwvid-migration-2  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-activedirectory-webservices  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-client-license-platform-service-migration  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-onecore-tiledatarepository  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-windows-appmanagement-migration  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-windows-appx-deployment-server  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-windows-audio-mmecore-other  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-windows-bth-user  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-windows-com-complus-setup  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-windows-deviceassociationframeworkmigration  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-windows-directoryservices-adam-client  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-windows-iis-rm  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-windows-mapscontrol-migration  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-windows-mup  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-windows-network-setup  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-windows-offlinefiles-core  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-windows-pnpmigration  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-windows-rasapi-mig  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-windows-rasserver-migplugin  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-windows-security-ngc-localaccountmigplugin  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-windows-shmig  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-windows-sxs  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-windows-tcpip  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-windows-terminalservices-appserver-licensing  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-windows-terminalservices-licenseserver  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-windows-textservicesframework-migration  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-windows-virtualization-vmswitch  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\sources\replacementmanifests\networkbridge  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\sources\replacementmanifests\networking-mpssvc-svc  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\sources\replacementmanifests\printing-localprinting-replacement  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\sources\replacementmanifests\sppmig  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\sources\replacementmanifests\windowssearchengine  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\sources\replacementmanifests\wpc  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-windows-offlinefiles-core\en-us  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-windows-shmig\en-us  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\sources\replacementmanifests\microsoft-windows-sxs\en-us  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\support  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\support\adfs  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\support\adprep  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\support\logging  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\support\samples  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\support\adfs\en-us  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\support\adprep\en-us  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
B:\support\logging\en-us  No permissions are set. All users have full control.
C:\
C:\WindowsImageBackup BUILTIN\Administrators:(OI)(CI)(F)
                      BUILTIN\Backup Operators:(OI)(CI)(F)
                      CREATOR OWNER:(OI)(CI)(F)

C:\WindowsImageBackup\FS BUILTIN\Administrators:(OI)(CI)(F)
                         BUILTIN\Backup Operators:(OI)(CI)(F)
                         CREATOR OWNER:(OI)(CI)(F)

C:\WindowsImageBackup\FS\Backup 2024-04-19 085051 BUILTIN\Administrators:(OI)(CI)(F)
                                                  BUILTIN\Backup Operators:(OI)(CI)(F)
                                                  CREATOR OWNER:(OI)(CI)(F)

C:\WindowsImageBackup\FS\Catalog BUILTIN\Administrators:(OI)(CI)(F)
                                 BUILTIN\Backup Operators:(OI)(CI)(F)
                                 CREATOR OWNER:(OI)(CI)(F)

C:\WindowsImageBackup\FS\Logs BUILTIN\Administrators:(OI)(CI)(F)
                              NT AUTHORITY\SYSTEM:(OI)(CI)(F)
                              BUILTIN\Backup Operators:(OI)(CI)(F)

C:\WindowsImageBackup\FS\SPPMetadataCache BUILTIN\Administrators:(OI)(CI)(F)
                                          BUILTIN\Backup Operators:(OI)(CI)(F)
                                          CREATOR OWNER:(OI)(CI)(F)

D:\
D:\Firma NT AUTHORITY\Authenticated Users:(RX)
         BUILTIN\Administrators:(I)(OI)(CI)(F)
         NT AUTHORITY\SYSTEM:(I)(OI)(CI)(F)
         CREATOR OWNER:(I)(OI)(CI)(IO)(F)
         KREDIT\Domain Admins:(I)(OI)(CI)(F)

D:\Firma\Direktion KREDIT\DL_Direktion_M:(OI)(CI)(RX,W,DC)
                   KREDIT\DL_Direktion_R:(OI)(CI)(RX)
                   BUILTIN\Administrators:(I)(OI)(CI)(F)
                   NT AUTHORITY\SYSTEM:(I)(OI)(CI)(F)
                   CREATOR OWNER:(I)(OI)(CI)(IO)(F)
                   KREDIT\Domain Admins:(I)(OI)(CI)(F)

D:\Firma\Indl?n KREDIT\DL_Indl?n_M:(OI)(CI)(RX,W,DC)
                KREDIT\DL_Indl?n_R:(OI)(CI)(RX)
                BUILTIN\Administrators:(I)(OI)(CI)(F)
                NT AUTHORITY\SYSTEM:(I)(OI)(CI)(F)
                CREATOR OWNER:(I)(OI)(CI)(IO)(F)
                KREDIT\Domain Admins:(I)(OI)(CI)(F)

D:\Firma\IT KREDIT\DL_IT_M:(OI)(CI)(RX,W,DC)
            KREDIT\DL_IT_R:(OI)(CI)(RX)
            BUILTIN\Administrators:(I)(OI)(CI)(F)
            NT AUTHORITY\SYSTEM:(I)(OI)(CI)(F)
            CREATOR OWNER:(I)(OI)(CI)(IO)(F)
            KREDIT\Domain Admins:(I)(OI)(CI)(F)

D:\Firma\IT Studentermedhj?lper KREDIT\DL_IT studentermedhj?lper_M:(OI)(CI)(RX,W,DC)
                                KREDIT\DL_IT studentermedhj?lper_R:(OI)(CI)(RX)
                                BUILTIN\Administrators:(I)(OI)(CI)(F)
                                NT AUTHORITY\SYSTEM:(I)(OI)(CI)(F)
                                CREATOR OWNER:(I)(OI)(CI)(IO)(F)
                                KREDIT\Domain Admins:(I)(OI)(CI)(F)

D:\Firma\ProjektLaundry KREDIT\DL_ProjektLaundry_M:(OI)(CI)(RX,W,DC)
                        KREDIT\DL_ProjektLaundry_R:(OI)(CI)(RX)
                        BUILTIN\Administrators:(I)(OI)(CI)(F)
                        NT AUTHORITY\SYSTEM:(I)(OI)(CI)(F)
                        CREATOR OWNER:(I)(OI)(CI)(IO)(F)
                        KREDIT\Domain Admins:(I)(OI)(CI)(F)

D:\Firma\ProjektTaxevation KREDIT\DL_ProjektTaxevation_M:(OI)(CI)(RX,W,DC)
                           KREDIT\DL_ProjektTexavation_R:(OI)(CI)(RX)
                           BUILTIN\Administrators:(I)(OI)(CI)(F)
                           NT AUTHORITY\SYSTEM:(I)(OI)(CI)(F)
                           CREATOR OWNER:(I)(OI)(CI)(IO)(F)
                           KREDIT\Domain Admins:(I)(OI)(CI)(F)

D:\Firma\Udl?n KREDIT\DL_Udl?n_M:(OI)(CI)(RX,W,DC)
               KREDIT\DL_Udl?n_R:(OI)(CI)(RX)
               BUILTIN\Administrators:(I)(OI)(CI)(F)
               NT AUTHORITY\SYSTEM:(I)(OI)(CI)(F)
               CREATOR OWNER:(I)(OI)(CI)(IO)(F)
               KREDIT\Domain Admins:(I)(OI)(CI)(F)

